<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Mjölk - Bookmarks</title>
  <link>http://blog.mjolk.net</link>
  <description>Mjölk project news</description>
      
  <item>
    <title>One up v0.3.1</title>
    <link>/01-29-2011/One-up-v031.html</link>
		<pubDate>Sat Jan 29 15:15:00 +0100 2011</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;h2&gt;One up : v0.3.1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beta release &lt;a href="https://github.com/mcansky/mjolk/tree/v0.3.1"&gt;v0.3.1 is out&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.mjolk.net"&gt;running&lt;/a&gt;. It features some interesting changes :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;api support with basic http auth (more on this later, check the rdoc v1/posts)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;fix the bookmarks deletion process when a user is deleting his account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can check the &lt;a href="https://github.com/mcansky/mjolk/blob/v0.3.1/CHANGELOG.md"&gt;Changelog&lt;/a&gt; on github.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, you are most welcome to comment, test, post issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
    
  <item>
    <title>Mjölk goes beta and live</title>
    <link>/01-28-2011/Mjolk-goes-beta-and-live.html</link>
		<pubDate>Fri Jan 28 15:15:00 +0100 2011</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;h2&gt;Mjölk goes beta and live&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone, this is first post of the Mjölk blog. Mjölk is a bookmarking engine licensed under &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MIT&lt;/span&gt; to bring a simple alternative to some big names.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mjölk is swedish for milk.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was mainly started to provide a safe harbor after the Delicious rumors. The goal was to create something that will be easily managed and perpetuated in all situations. But now it&#8217;s somehow different with a code base growing quickly and some ideas running.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are working a lot to finish the first set of functionnalities but already there the really basic ones : bookmark with tags, tag clouds, private bookmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The registration is open, with a 42 beta testers quota. After that (about 30 seats left right now) we will lock any new accounts until we finish some stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then some news will come here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
    

</channel>

</rss>
